双峰
第三季第三集
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     苏小黛   桃小兔   Reginamoon   Lynn_宁
翻译     TheWalkingNerd   一只虾   小酸奶
校对     小酸奶
时间轴     吃土少女   啾啾啾
后期     8T
总监     小酸奶
这是哪
Where is this?
我们在哪
Where are we?
蓝色玫瑰
等你到了那里
你将
已经在那里了
你最好赶快
我妈妈要来了
罗莎牧场
道吉  你的胳膊怎么了
Dougie, what is wrong with your arm?
我不知道
I don't know.
我觉得它睡着了
I think it fell asleep.
有点刺痛
It's sort of tingly.
我也有点刺痛
I'm kind of tingly, too.
我要去洗洗  好吗
I'm gonna go wash up, okay?
怎么回事
What the fuck was that?
道吉
Dougie!
我觉得  很有趣
I feel... funny.
我怎么了
What's happening to me?
有人
制造了
你
什么
What?
为了一个目的
但是
我认为
现在
那目的已经
实现了
是吗
It has?
真奇怪
That's weird.
那是什么声音  道吉
What was that noise, Dougie?
你在哪
Where are you?
道吉
Dougie?
我的天
Oh, my God.
道吉  搞什么
Dougie, what the hell?
你从哪弄的那西装...
Where'd you get that suit...
还有发型
and haircut?
难道你一直都戴着假发吗  道吉
Have you been wearing a rug all this time, Dougie?
天啊  你病了吗  道吉
Oh, my God, are you sick, Dougie?
快起来  我们得出门了
Come on, we got to get out of this house.
快点儿啊  道吉
Come on, Dougie!
道吉
Dougie.
道吉  你是不是忘了什么
Dougie, did you forget something?
你的鞋呢
Your shoes?
我去拿吧
I'll get them.
道吉
Dougie!
别闹了行吗
Could you quit fucking around?
把你的鞋穿上  给
And put on your shoes. Here.
把你鞋穿上
Put on your damn shoes!
快点  我们走
Come on, let's go.
好吧
All right...
你带了钥匙吧
You do have your keys, right?
你是说杰德要捎你两程吗
You mean Jade has to give you two rides?
她刚开着一辆吉普牧马人走了
Yeah, she just drove by in a Wrangler.
看上去好像有两个人  但是...
Looked like maybe two people, but...
他的车还在这里
his car's still here.
我在入口处准备就绪了
I'm all set near the entrance.
如果他在车里  我就把他带过来
If he's in the car, I'll get him here.
等你找到钱包
Once you find your wallet
或是手机
or your cell phone,
公用电话  或是搞到点钱
a pay phone or some money,
你就打给拖车公司  道吉
you can call AAA, Dougie.
他们会帮你的
They will help you.
梧桐街36800号
杰德会稍我两程
Jade give two rides.
天呐
Oh, my God.
前方有减速带
基恩...
Gene...
他不在车里
he's not in the car.
他肯定还在屋里
Yeah, he must still be inside.
我去给他的车装追踪器
I'll load up his car. -
好
All right.
咱们麦基家见
I'll see you at Mikey's.
一一九
One-one-nine!
怎么回事  比利
What the hell, Billy?
天啊  里面臭死了
Oh, God, something awful's in there.
调度中心
Dispatch.
我们需要一辆救护车
We need an ambulance.
让他们带上防毒面具
And tell them to bring gas masks.
车里的味道很难闻
There is something bad in this vehicle.
过来
Come here.
你不会有事的
You'll be all right.
双峰镇警察局
欢迎骚扰
我们把所有东西都摆出来了  霍克
We laid everything out, Hawk,
但没发现丢了的东西
and we can't find anything that's missing.
假如东西不在这里  那么...
If it's not here, then...
你怎么知道它不见了
how do you know it's missing?
但假如东西在这里...
But if it is here...
那就说明没有丢
then it isn't missing?
这个...
This...
是在这里的
is here.
让我们坐下吧
Let's sit down.
让...
Let--
我坐下吧
let me sit down.
让我们从头开始
Let's start from the beginning.
-而且...  -别说话
- And-- - Don't say a thing.
我得把我的想法说出来
I need to think out loud.
有东西不见了  我得把它找出来
Something is missing, and I need to find it.
而我找到它的方式
And the way I'm gonna find it
和我的遗产有关
has something to do with my heritage.
你是个印第安人
You're an Indian.
是的  露西
Yes, Lucy.
显然...
And apparently...
我就是要通过那种方式来弄明白不见的是什么
that's the way I'm gonna find what's missing.
小兔子巧克力
怎么了
What is it?
你还好吗  小甜甜
Are you okay, punky?
我知道什么东西不见了
I know what's missing!
什么
What's missing?
小兔子
The bunny!
The bunny.
我吃了小兔子
I ate that bunny!
小兔子巧克力
不见的就是它
That's missing.
就是它不见了
小兔子巧克力
Do chocolate bunnies
跟你的遗产有任何关联吗
have anything to do with your heritage?
没有
No.
跟小兔子没关系
It's not about the bunny.
你把证据吃了  露西
You ate the evidence, Lucy?
我知道
I know!
那是唯一一次
I never did it again.
我也只吃了一个
And I only ate one.
我从没有再犯了
And I never did it again.
但我当时出了点毛病...
But I had a problem at that time with--
我也不想当着安迪面说
And I don't like to say this in front of Andy.
但我当时有一点
But I had a bubble...
胀气
of gas.
我听说
And I had read...
有时候我爱吃的
...that sometimes chocolate,
巧克力
which I love,
可以当作一种疗方
can be used as a remedy,
或许是土著民族发明的
maybe by indigenous people.
是这样吗  霍克
Is that true, Hawk?
你们吃巧克力来治疗胀气吗
Do you use chocolate as a remedy for gas?
你想不想再吃点小兔子  乖乖
Do you want another bunny, punky?
我可以再给你拿一点
I can get you more bunnies.
跟小兔子没关系
It's not about the bunny.
小兔子巧克力
会跟小兔子有关吗
Is it about the bunny?
不
No.
跟小兔子没关系
It's not about the bunny.
银色野马赌场
好了
All right.
进去吧  道吉
Go inside, Dougie.
里面有人会帮你的
Someone will help you in there.
-那里面  -对
- In there. - Right.
我想你该试着忘记遇见我的事
And I think you should try to forget you ever met me.
应该不会太为难你
Shouldn't be too hard for you.
给你五美元
Now, here's $5.
去找人帮忙
Call for help.
找人帮忙
没错
Right.
我觉得你应该请个医生什么的
And I think you should maybe call a doctor or something
我猜你可能有点中风或其他问题
because I think you might've had a little stroke or something.
其他问题
Something.
是的
Yes.
你可以走了
You can go out now.
道吉  走啊
Dougie, go.
赶紧的  下车吧
Come on, let's get you out of here.
快  走吧  道吉
Come on. Let's go, Dougie.
对  走吧
Right, right.
银色野马赌场
找人帮忙
Call for help.
在里面  杰克
In the back, Jack.
嘿
Hey!
你要换一些零钱
You're gonna need some change.
一些零钱
Some change.
你要换成怎样的  你准备玩游戏吗
Well, how do you want it? You gonna play a game?
游戏
Game.
你准备玩什么游戏
What game are you gonna play?
找人帮忙
Call for help.
你们好
Hello!
Hello.
你中奖了
You broke that one.
而且是大奖啊
You broke it real good.
中奖了
Broke it.
是的  没错  兄弟
Sure did, pal.
你们好
Hello!
彩池  超大累积奖金
Mega, mega jackpot.
恭喜  先生
Congratulations, sir.
你是大赢家
You are a mega winner.
你刚赢了两个超大累积奖金
You've just won two mega jackpots
总金额是28400美元
for a total of $28,400.
不仅仅是这些
It's much more than these quarters.
找人帮忙
Call for help.
我就是为此来找你的
Oh, well, that's what I'm here for.
我给你拿个更大的篮子
Let me get you a bigger bucket.
不行
No.
那个傻子走了
The nutcake left.
乔  看住这台机子
Joe, you watch this one.
你好
Hello!
宾夕法尼亚州  费城  联调局总部
艾伯特
Albert?
他现在正式被控
He's been officially accused now
残忍谋杀他的妻子
of brutally murdering his wife.
他声称自己是无辜的  知道是谁干的
He claims he's innocent and knows who did it,
但不能说  因为会泄露国家机密
but can't say because it would breach national security.
不管怎么样
However...
他要告诉克里斯  这些他放在
he got word to Chris here that these items,
乔治敦花园中的东西
which he placed in his garden in Georgetown,
是查出凶手身份的关键
are the clues to the identity of the killer.
议员的困境
The congressman's dilemma.
好了  你们都去干活吧
All right, you all can go get to work on this.
塔米  你留下来
And, Tammy, you stay
跟我和艾伯特说说你在纽约发现了什么
and show me and Albert what you found in New York.
谢谢你们
Thank you all.
不客气
You're welcome.
纽约警局不知道到底发生了什么
NYPD doesn't have a clue what was going on here.
他们甚至不知道这地方是谁的
They don't even know who owns the place.
那里之前全天候24小时都有门卫看守
Apparently there were guards on duty 24-7,
但现在一个都不见了
but they can't find any of them--
只能确认死者山姆·科尔比
Only the victims-- Sam Colby, Tracey Barberato--
和特雷茜·巴伯拉多的身份
have been ID'd.
他们还收缴了还几百卷
They confiscated hundreds of digital files
从不同角度拍这个玻璃箱的录像
showing various angles of this glass box.
曾经出现过一些模糊的影子
Once in a while, they show some blurred shape pass through,
但是只有几帧
but only a few frames.
然后凶案发生当晚
Then on the night of the murders,
录像中出现了这个
on camera, this appears.
什么东西
What the hell?
其他相机什么都没拍到
The other cameras saw nothing.
这个东西一动
And as soon as this thing moved,
就消失了
it disappeared.
法医怎么说
Forensics?
尸体被残忍肢解了
The bodies were violently mutilated,
但是没有留下任何指纹  DNA和纤维
but no prints, no DNA, no fibers.
十分干净
Completely clean.
什么都没留下
Nothing.
科尔局长
Director Cole?
有您的电话  是库柏打来的
On your phone, it's Cooper.
什么
What?
有您的电话  是库柏打来的
On your phone, it's Cooper.
艾伯特
Albert.
我是科尔
This is Cole.
好的  我等着
Yes, I'll hold.
-是他吗  -什么
- Is it him? - What?
是他吗
Is it him?
是的  我能听到
Yes, I hear you.
什么
What?
哪里
Where?
你确定是他吗
Are you sure it's him?
"麻烦"是什么意思
What do you mean "Trouble"?
好  我们明天早上第一件事就是去那
All right, we'll be out there first thing tomorrow morning.
九点整安排一次会谈
Set up an interview for nine o'clock sharp.
艾伯特  我们去
Albert, we're headed
南达科他州的黑丘
for the Black Hills of South Dakota.
黑丘
The Black Hills?
真的吗
Seriously?
虽然这消息让我们很开心  艾伯特
As happy as this news makes us, Albert,
但不能让别人知道
we can't put this on the radio.
很好
Perfect.
我一直很想看看拉什莫尔山
I've been dying to see Mount Rushmore.
你想快点  这很好
It's good you want to hurry.
我们天一亮就起飞
We fly at dawn,
塔米  你和我们一起去
and, Tammy, you're coming with us.
存在的有着奇怪力量的荒诞的神秘事物
The absurd mystery of the strange forces of existence.
满满一卡车的安定怎么样
How about a truckload full of Valium?
枪炮酒吧